A human's nose
is never as sensitive as a dog's.
My Lord,
this concerns His Majesty's safety.
We cannot afford any delay.
You all stay here.
You, come with me.
What is this pill made of?
Lead the way.
Everyone, be careful.
Pulling out the heads and picking the vegetables,
the world becomes a better place.
Three thousand locks in the Zhimi Pavilion.
Five hundred strings of cash,
breaking heads.
This is a nursery rhyme circulating in the streets.
It mocks those high officials
who oppress the people.
Taoist,
Should we
just go back?
You must be the Master of Wuyou Cave.
We are all in the same circle.
Why play these tricks to mystify things?
So you are the distinguished disciple of Master Luo from Erxian Mountain.
I failed to recognize a great person.
Everyone, please calm down.
I have a small matter to deal with first.
An old customer wanted to sleep with the bride
and asked me to kidnap her.
But he only paid Wuyou City half the silver.
So,
I can only give him half.
Cave Chief,
why be like this?
We can just discuss business at the table.
Cave Chief.
The rules of Wuyou City are,
if a guest doesn't sit,
they shouldn't speak.
If no wine is drunk,
no business is done.
Then thank you, Cave Chief, for your hospitality.
Uncle Chai has depended on dogs since childhood.
Sensitive sense of smell.
I want to see where Liu Heizi can run to.
I want him alive.
Master.
The wine has gone down.
Now,
can I talk to you?
Please.
On the night of the Lantern Festival,
if you could get us
into the West Building of Fanlou,
we are willing to offer you 10,000 strings of cash.
If your sincerity is only gold and silver,
there is no need to talk further.
Master.
Perhaps you have other wishes.
As long as we Liangshan
can help you achieve it.
Absolutely.
Map of Dongjing City.
Privately drawing maps is a capital crime.
How could Wuyou City have such a thing?
Cave Master,
why are you showing this
map of Dongjing City?
To be honest, Daoist,
I have an enemy
named Shedaoren.
Over the years, he has amassed wealth through waterways.
Unfortunately, we have a gentleman's agreement
to stay out of each other's way.
Today,
since I've met you all,
I want to use your hands
to ruin his business.
There are only two days left until the Shangyuan Festival.
If you won't accept my terms,
then you can find someone else.
My Wuyou Cave...
I will never force you to stay.
What does the Cave Master need us to do?
Just say it directly.
My rival is involved in smuggling salt
and human trafficking.
This river
is the channel they use to transport smuggled salt
and trafficked women into Dongjing City.
Bian River.
Brother Meng,
what's so special
about this Bian River?
You are not from Dongjing,
so you don't know.
This Bian River
not only handles water transport,
but also the gold, silver, spices,
tribute tea, and so on from the south.
Even the flowers and stones used by the emperor
are transported to the capital through it.
The emperor attaches great importance to this Bian River.
Around the Bian River,
a large-scale patrol force is deployed,
stationed along the river.
Sometimes,
even the imperial guards are mobilized
to participate in the patrol.
Normally,
not even a fly
could fly over the Bian River.
Those doing business on the Bian River,
I am afraid,
their boats have hidden compartments at the bottom.
Smuggled salt and drugged women
are placed inside.
So, whether by their appearance
or by boarding inspections,
you can't see anything unusual.
What I want you to do
is to expose his business
to the world.
It's best to make it known
to the whole city.
Okay.
We'll help you fulfill your wish, Cave Master.
But
you must also keep your promise to us.
Cave Master,
I also have a favor to ask.
Tell me.
On my way here,
I saw an old man looking for his daughter.
Do you know her whereabouts?
Daughter?
Are you talking about the lantern bearer?
Exactly.
So he didn't just survive,
he hasn't given up either.
Please tell me, Cave Master.
I'd appreciate it.
Your gratitude is worthless to me.
What's the use of it?
I can help ruin your rival's business.
That's between the Taoist priest and me.
It has nothing to do with you.
If you insist on asking,
you'll have to make
another deal with me.
Then,
wait for me
to finish their business,
and I'll come back to you.
Your good karma has arrived.
Young man,
any news about my daughter?
I've asked the Master of Wuyou Cave.
Wait a couple more days.
Did the Master of Wuyou Cave
make any harsh demands?
He
asked me to do something for him
before he'd help me.
Do you need my help?
No need.
I'll help them finish their task first,
then I'll help you find your daughter.
Your great kindness, young man,
even if my body is smashed to pieces,
I will repay.
Old man,
wait until you're reunited with your daughter
before thanking me.
Okay.
I'll take your word for it.
Hurry up and go.
Young man Meng,
don't let external matters disturb you.
Take care, old man.
He really treats himself like a dog.
Every time I see him,
I feel extremely disgusted.
What is the most important duty of our Bingjingwu?
To protect the safety of the imperial city.
For villains like him,
as long as they are useful,
they are acceptable.
Understood.
Brother Meng.
You're known as the geography expert.
Why don't you tell us more about the Bian River?
The Bian River is 40 zhang wide and 6 chi deep.
As I said before,
the government attaches great importance to it.
Patrols inspect it day and night.
If you are not absolutely sure,
don't act rashly.
Brother Meng.
Don't worry about that.
With my brother Li Lang here,
the Bian River is nothing.
My title 'White Streak in the Waves'
is truly well-deserved.
Shh.
Someone is coming.
And more than one.
Liu Heizi.